musthavemenus.com 2018-12-02

# MustHaveMenus Privacy Policy

MustHaveMenus values your privacy. You may contact us any time to learn more about this privacy policy by sending an email to Contact@MustHaveMenus.com. This Privacy Statement describes how MustHaveMenus.com collects and uses information about you when you use the MustHaveMenus.com web site ("Site"). 

### What type of information is collected from you?

We collect information that personally identifies you or allows us to contact you when you register to use the Site. Such information may include your name, e-mail address, user password and other information (collectively "Personal Information"). You may also provide us with Personal Information when submitting orders for our services, including your credit card information, billing address, and shipping information. MustHaveMenus uses your Personal Information to operate the Site, to affect your transactions initiated at the Site, and to study and improve our services. You may correct or update your Personal Information by editing your My Account page or by sending an e-mail to [Contact@MustHaveMenus.com](mailto:Contact@MustHaveMenus.com).

**Google Analytics Demographics**

MustHaveMenus uses data collected from Google's Analytics to better understand our customer needs and improve our service and products. You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads on Google's site, go to [_Ad Settings_](https://www.google.com/settings/ads) or use [_other opt-out settings_](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

### How is your information used?

MustHaveMenus primarily uses your information to process orders that you have submitted for our Services. We also use your information to provide you customer service, send you order processing information, and to notify you of changes to our service. We may also from time to time send you information about special offers, however, we make our best efforts to send promotions on an opt-in basis only. 

You can stop delivery of promotional information from MustHaveMenus by using the UNSUBSCRIBE link provided in all marketing emails, or by sending an e-mail to [Contact@MustHaveMenus.com](mailto:Contact@MustHaveMenus.com).

### Who has access to your information?

We will not sell or rent your information to third parties without your express permission. In general, we are not in the business of selling personal information. We only consider this type of business when it directly relates to a product or service we believe complements our existing services and will be truly valuable to our customers.

**Third Party Service Providers**

We partner with other companies to support the MustHaveMenus product lines and these service providers may come into contact with your Personal Information. For example, we use third party software to help with our customer service and we use a payments company to process our transactions. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing the services of MustHaveMenus.

**Other Situations in which Personal Information May Be Disclosed**

We may store and disclose Personal Information as required by applicable law or to be in compliance with government regulations. We may make disclosures that are necessary or advisable to conform to legal and regulatory requirements and to protect the rights, safety and property of MustHaveMenus, users of the Site, and the public.

### Security

We take reasonable, industry-standard steps to protect Personal Information and use technology such as SSL encryption, passwords, access control procedures, and firewalls, as well as physical security.

### Use of 'Cookies'

You must have Cookies turned ON to be a member at MustHaveMenus. Cookies are very small text files saved to your local drive. They serve as your identification and are uniquely yours. A cookie can only be read by the server that gave it to you. Cookies tell us that you returned to a specific web page on our Site, and help us track your preferences. Cookies enable you to login, maintain stored versions of your work, and help us personalize your experience at the Site.

### Data Retention

We retain personal data as long as it may be relevant to providing the MustHaveMenus services. To dispose of personal data, we may anonymize it, delete it or take other appropriate steps. Data may persist in backup copies for recovery purposes.

### Children's Privacy

Children under the age of 13 are not allowed to purchase products on the Site. MustHaveMenus does not knowingly collect Personal Information about children under the age of 13 or allow them to place orders on the Site. If we learn of such behavior, MustHaveMenus will close the child's account and delete all information collected about that person. Notwithstanding the foregoing, MustHaveMenus may choose to retain the child's e-mail address as a means to prevent the child from re-registering with MustHaveMenus.

### Your Rights

Under the [General Data Protection Regulation](http://eur-lex.europa.eu/legal-content/EN/TXT/PDF/?uri=CELEX:32016R0679&from=EN) you have a number of important rights. In summary, those include rights to: 

  1. The right to be informed. This means anyone processing your personal data must make clear what they are processing, why, and who else the data may be passed to. 
  2. The right to see what data is being stored about you. 
  3. The right to have your data corrected or amended if what is held is incorrect in some way. 
  4. The right to be forgotten. Under certain circumstances you can ask for your personal data to be deleted. This would apply if the personal data is no longer required for the purposes it was collected for, or your consent for the processing of that data has been withdrawn, or the personal data has been unlawfully processed. 
  5. The right to ask for a temporary halt to processing of personal data, such as in the case where a dispute or legal case has to be concluded, or the data is being corrected. 
  6. The right to ask for any data stored to be provided in a structured, commonly used, and machine-readable format. 
  7. The right to object to further processing of your data in ways inconsistent with the primary purpose for which it was collected, including profiling, automation, and direct marketing. 

## Changes to the MustHaveMenus Privacy Policy Statement

MustHaveMenus may make changes to this Privacy Statement from time to time. We will post changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. We may also notify you of significant changes by e-mail, on the site, or in other ways.

**

Questions, Comments, Concerns

**

If you have any questions or comments about our use of Personal Information, please contact us at [Contact@MustHaveMenus.com](mailto:Contact@MustHaveMenus.com). We will use reasonable efforts to promptly investigate any complaint you may have regarding our use of Personal Information.
